// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "According the Sri Lankan motor traffic law, accidental warning signals are in,",
    answer: "Black colour with Yellow background",
    options: [
      "White colour with Red background",
      "Black colour with Yellow background",
      "Red colour with White background",
      "White colour with Blue background"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "The primary rule of a roundabout is?",
    answer: "Give away the road to the vehicles coming from the right",
    options: [
      "Give away the road to the vehicles coming from left or close to the vehicle",
      "Give away the road to the vehicles coming from the most jammed direction",
      "Give away the road to the vehicles coming from right or closely by right side",
      "Give away the road to the vehicles coming from the right",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: " When you drive forward on a road with three lanes, what you should select is?",
    answer: "Middle lane of the road",
    options: [
      "Right lane of the road",
      "Left lane of the road",
      "Middle lane of the road",
      "Middle lane or the right lane of the road",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: " You should keep an adequate distance with the front vehicle,",
    answer: "Because if the front vehicle driver suddenly stops, you can safely control your vehicle",
    options: [
      "Because if the front vehicle driver suddenly stops, you can safely control your vehicle",
      "Because the front vehicle receives much space to overtake",
      "Because it is easy drive behind the front vehicle",
      "Because if the front vehicle driver suddenly stops, you have more time to overtake",
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Hazard lamps of a vehicle should use,",
    answer: "Only when a vehicle is disabled and stopped.",
    options: [
      "To indicate the vehicle is having an emergency situation",
      "When a vehicle drive straight in an intersection",
      "To get the priority",
      "Only when a vehicle is disabled and stopped.",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "When another vehicle overtakes your vehicle,",
    answer: "Let the other vehicle to overtake you without increasing the speed",
    options: [
      "Ready to stop by lowering the gears",
      "Let the other vehicle to overtake you without increasing the speed",
      "If you are not willing to let him to overtake, you can increase the speed",
      "If you are not willing to let him to overtake, right hand signal can be shown",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "When there is a yellow box in a junction,",
    answer: "Except in a right turn, if the entry is blocked, should not enter the yellow box",
    options: [
      "Except in a right turn, if the entry is blocked, should not enter the yellow box",
      "You can enter the yellow box anytime except in a right turn",
      "You can enter the yellow box anytime",
     "You can enter the yellow box if you drive straight",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "A place to park the vehicle",
    answer: "25 meters away from an intersection",
    options: [
      "20 meters away from a bus halt",
      "On a spiral area of a pedestrian crossing or 10 meters away from such spiral area of a pedestrian crossing",
      "10 meters away from fire water pipe",
      "25 meters away from an intersection"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "You should not overtake another vehicle",
    answer: "On a pedestrian crossing or closer",
    options: [
      "In front of a court or nearby",
      "When not cutting the broken lines on the road",
      "On a pedestrian crossing or closer",
      "In front of a hospital or closer",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "If your vehicle faces a hazard,",
    answer: "You can use the vehicle to transport the victims after marking the accident signs on the road",
    options: [
      "You can use the vehicle to transport the victims after marking the accident signs on the road",
      "The vehicles should not move away until a policeman comes",
      "Immediately the vehicle should be taken away and check whether it has technical issues",
      "Immediately the vehicle should be taken away and report to the police",
    ]
  },

  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];